nighslee.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy and Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the information practices of Nighslee (hereinafter "we," "us," or "our"). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what information we collect from you, how we use and share such information, and the choices you have regarding our collection and use. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you when you visit or use our Websites, and other online forums ("Online Services").

## YOUR CONSENT

BY ACCESSING OUR ONLINE SERVICES, PURCHASING OUR PRODUCTS, AND COMMUNICATING OR OTHERWISE INTERACTING WITH US, YOU KNOWINGLY ACCEPT AND CONSENT TO THE INFORMATION PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

## INFORMATION COVERED

This Privacy Policy applies to information collected about you by Nighslee. As used herein, "Personal Information" means information that personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, phone number or credit card number, and "Non-Personal Information" means information that relates to you but does not directly identify you. "Information" is collectively used herein to refer to both Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any third parties or any Websites that might be linked to our Online Services or products. 

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT

Nighslee collects Information about you from a variety of sources, including Personal Information you provide directly to us when you order, purchase, or register a product, request information or samples, or otherwise communicate with us, and Information we collect about you when you access or use our Online Services and otherwise interact with us. We also collect Information about you from third parties including other online services and our business partners. We may combine any of the Information collected about you for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

### Personal Information

We do not collect Personal Information from you unless you voluntarily provide such information to us. Personal Information includes your name, shipping and billing addresses, e-mail address, credit card information, and/or phone number. Each of which is a piece of your Personal Information and we collect variable amounts of Personal Information based on how your engagement with us. Some of the places we collect Personal Information are when you order a product from us, register your product, create an online account, request or subscribe to catalogues, product information, contact or communicate with us, submit a product review, testimonial, comment, suggestion, or other content to us, and/or otherwise interact with us online or by phone, mail, chat, or in person. Based on how you interact with us and the information you share, we use the Personal Information we collect to process and communicate with you about your order, ship the products you ordered, process credit card payments, enhance your shopping experience, and for other marketing and research purposes. To help protect against fraud and identity theft, we reserve the right to request proof of identification upon any purchase.

### Information We Receive from Third Parties

We may receive Information about you from third parties. For example, if you access our Online Services through a third-party connection or log-in (e.g., through social media), such third party may pass certain information about your use of its service to us. We may also obtain other Information about you such as change of address, contact information, or demographic information from commercially or publicly available sources.

### Information Collected Automatically

Our Online Services use a variety of tracking technologies that may include, but not limited to cookies, location data, online analytics (hereinafter, “Tracking Tools”) to automatically collect Information from you. Tracking Tools are used for a variety of purposes, including enhancing your online experience and our product offerings. Information collected from these Tracking Tools will be treated and considered as Non-Personal Information.

IMPORTANT: BY USING OUR SITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT ALL PERSONAL DATA SUBMITTED TO US MAY BE PROCESSED BY US AS NOTED HEREIN. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, DISCONTINUE USE OF THE SITE IMMEDIATELY.

## HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED

Nighslee uses your Information, for a range of purposes, including providing our products to you and other product related tasks. Upon using our Site and engaging in a transaction, you consent to us collecting and using your personal information to; complete transactions, delivery, communication, improve our Website, improve our promotional and material operations, offer a wider selection of products, and customize our Site’s content, layout, and services for your convenience and extended use. Upon receiving your personal information you give us explicit consent to send you marketing and promotional material to your inbox. If you no longer wish to receive these emails or agree to receive these emails, you may unsubscribe to them. for more information on how to do so, contact our support: [contact@nighslee.com](mailto:contact@nighslee.com) We may combine all the Information we collect or receive about you for any of the foregoing purposes.

## HOW WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

The Website may include external links to websites of our affiliates or other third parties. We cannot warrant the use of external sites. These websites may collect information about you and use the information which may differ from our Privacy Policy. If you do visit any external link, it is your responsibility to consult that website’s privacy policy, as once you are outside the Website, we have no authority over their usage and collection of data.

If Nighslee or this Site is acquired or merges with another company, your information will be transferred to the new owners.

In rare cases, we may be required by judicial authorities or law enforcement to provide sensitive information during an ongoing investigation. In these rare events, we will only disclose your information to the extent necessary for the investigation. We will fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying any user who uses any of our services for illegal activities and reserve the explicit right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities believed to be unlawful. We may disclose your information as necessary if you violate our Terms of Use or any other Agreement with us.

We will not sell, trade, or rent your Information to any third-party.

## SOCIAL MEDIA / PRODUCT REVIEWS

Any Information such as a product review, testimonial, or comment, to social media platforms such as Facebook, blogs, etc., or using a share feature could be seen, collected, and used by anyone who has access, including, without limitation, your user/screen name. Any Information, including Personal Information, which you post via our Online Services or social media platforms, you maintain full responsibility for. Any Information you share or otherwise post becomes public information and will not be subject to this Privacy Policy. 

## YOUR CHOICES

At any time, you may contact our support if you wish to; access your Information, change your personal Information or remove yourself for any marketing or promotional activity.

Contact us for more information about privacy concerns: [contact@nighslee.com](mailto:contact@nighslee.com) I could take up to several weeks for any change to be made.

If we are unable to collect your personal information, please be aware you may not receive any special deals, promotions or information about new products. 

## INFORMATION SECURITY

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your login information. This includes your password. We encourage our users to actively change their passwords periodically to avoid unauthorized access to any account you have with us.

In the rare event that any Personal Information under our control is compromised, Nighslee will take the necessary steps to investigate the situation. Any attempt to solicit personal information which does not belong to you will result in action being taken in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

## OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES

Our Online Services are provided from within the United States and are subject to the state and federal laws of the United States. If you are located outside the United States, your information is being collected and stored in the United States. Our Terms and Agreements may not be applicable to foreign law. If you do not agree with this, please do not use our Online Services.

## CALIFORNIA RESIDENT PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a California resident, you have the right to request a Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure once per year which will identify the third parties with whom we or any of our affiliates has shared Personal Information collected from you. You may request the Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure by writing to us at [contact@nighslee.com](mailto:contact@nighslee.com). We will respond to your request for a Notice of Information-Sharing Disclosure within 30 days.

## CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

We do not knowingly solicit or collect Personal Information online from children under the age of 13 without consent from parents or guardians. Please contact us if you believe any information was collected without parental or guardian consent

## EMAIL SECURITY

If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your Personal Information, please notify us as provided below in the Contact Us section. This is more than likely a “phishing” attempting to steal personal information.

## RIGHT TO CHANGES

This Privacy Policy may change without notice. It is your responsibility to keep yourself updated with any changes to this policy by referring to the date above. By continued use of the Site and its services, you agree and acknowledge any changes to this policy, terms or agreements made on this site.

## CONTACT

If you have any questions or concerns about the aforementioned Terms or Policies, please be sure to contact us: [contact@nighslee.com](mailto:contact@nighslee.com)
